<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn on Internet of Me</title>
    <link>http://jerad.xyz/tags/learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learn on Internet of Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jerad Acosta</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 19:37:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jerad.xyz/tags/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Notebook Basics</title>
      <link>http://jerad.xyz/post/jupyter-notebook-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 19:37:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jerad.xyz/post/jupyter-notebook-basics/</guid>
      <description>Some notes to keep handy as a reminder of the basics in using a Jupyter notebook
What is a Jupyter notebook? According to the Web App&amp;rsquo;s main page: The Jupyter Notebook is an open-source web application that allows you to create and share documents that contain live code, equations, visualizations and explanatory text. Uses include: data cleaning and transformation, numerical simulation, statistical modeling, machine learning and much more.
In my own words: Application for creating and sharing documents that contain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wharton Operations Analytics Notes</title>
      <link>http://jerad.xyz/post/wharton-operations-analytics-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jerad.xyz/post/wharton-operations-analytics-notes/</guid>
      <description>Operations Analytics Notes for Week 1:  The descriptive analytics covered this week will provide a strong conceptual basis for predictive and prescriptive analytics in the following three weeks of the course.
 Covered by this Courser The class will start by going over a number of the most important and familiar problems in operations. The Newsvendor Problem is one of the fundamental problems in operations. We will also cover a range of related problems such as Resource Allocation, Network Management and Capacity Planning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>